Preliminary Guide to the Gelman Library Administration records, ca. 1825-2005 RG0119
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Renaissance Times, 1984-2007; RG0119 Series 13; 19.5 Linear feet (Box 2, Box 3, Box 1, Box 6, Box 7, Box 4, Box 5, Box 14, Box 11, Box 10, Box 9, Box 8, Box 13, Box 12)
  This series includes the Renaissance Times library newsletter from 1984-2005.
  Formerly ACC#392
  - Volume 1, No.1-60, 07/17/1984-09/10/1985 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    No.26: January 7, 1985 and January 15, 1985; Volume 1 is actually numbered by issue
  - Volume 2, No.9-50, 09/17/1985-06/24/1986 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    No.12: October 8, 1985 and October 15, 1985; From September 17, 1985, RT has been in Volume System
  - Volume 3, No.1-9, 07/01/1986-08/26/1986 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Volume 3, No.10-55, 09/02/1986-07/14/1987 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Volume 4, No.3-26, 09/21/1987-12/29/1987 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Volume 4, No.27-52, 01/05/1988-06/28/1988 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Volume 5, No.1-26, 07/05/1988-12/27/1988 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Volume 6, No.1-51, 01/03/1989-12/27/1989 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    No.21 (May 30, 1989) and No.25 (June 6, 1989) there are probably no No.22, No.23, and No.24; No. 31 July 17, July 25, and August 1, 1989; No.36 September 5 and 12, 1989
  - Volume 7, No.1-25, 01/09/1990-06/26/1990 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Volume 8, No.1-51, 07/02/1990-06/25/1991 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    No.38, March 19, 1991 and March 26, 1991
  - Volume 9, No.1-53, 07/02/1991-06/30/1992 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    No.35 missing; 1990-1993 Strategic Plan in this file
  - Volume 10, No.1-74, 07/07/1992-12/28/1993 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    No.22, 29, and 57 missing
  - Volume 10, No.1-22, 01/04/1994-05/31/1994 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Volume 10, No.23-53, 06/07/1994-12/27/1994 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    No.25, June 21, 1994 and No.28, June 28, 1994, Volume number should be 11
  - Volume 10, No.1-52, 01/03/1995-12/29/1995 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    Missing Numbers: No.23, 24, Volume numbers should be 12
  - Volume 11, No.1-50, 01/08/1996-12/23/1996 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    Volume number should be 13
  - Volume 12, No.1-39, 01/06/1997-09/30/1997 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    Volume number should be 14
  - Volume 12, No.40-50, 10/07/1997-12/16/1997 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Volume 13, No.1-46, 01/06/1998-12/22/1998 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    No.12 missing, volume number should be 15
  - Volume 14, No.1-44, 01/05/1999-12/21/1999 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    Volume number should be 16
  - Volume 15, No.1-39, 01/04/2000-12/19/2000 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    Volume number should be 17
  - Volume 16, No.1-22, 01/04/2001-12/20/2000 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Volume 17, No.1-13, 01/05/2002-11/12/2002 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Volume 18, No.1-19, 01/23/2003-10/16/2003 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Volume 18, No.20-22, 11/06/2003-12/29/2003 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Volume 19, No.1-13, 01/22/2004-12/02/2004 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Volume 20, No.1-3; Volume 21, No.1, 01/13/2005-08/09/2005 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Volume 22, No.5; Volume 20, No. 6, 09/21/2005-10/07/2005 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Volume 20, No.7-9, 11/08/2005-12/08/2005 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Volume 21, No.1-9, 02/03/2006-12/08/2006 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    Issue 7 not published
  - Volume 22, No.1-, 02/09/2007- (Box 14, Folder 3)
- Systems project, RG0119 Series 14; 1.5 Linear feet (Box 1)
  This series includes library systems project - Blackwell.
  Formerly ACC#429
- Photographs, 1995; RG0119 Series 15; .25 Linear feet
  Photographs for university librarian Debbie Masters' farewell party in 1995.
  Formerly ACC#436. As of June 11, 2007, this series shares a box with RG0119/030 (formerly Acc582) and RG0119/031 (formerly Acc592)
- Event materials, 1964-1990; RG0119 Series 16; 1.5 Linear feet (Box 1)
  This series includes parent's weekend materials from 1964-1990.
  Formerly ACC#437
- Proposals, 1984-1986; RG0119 Series 17; 1.5 Linear feet
  This series includes systems proposals and automation at library materials from 1984-1986.
  Formerly ACC#454
- Office records, 1987; RG0119 Series 18; 1.5 Linear feet (Box 1)
  This series includes information on library update, renovation project, one millionth volume, and self-guided tour from 1987.
  Formerly ACC#442
- Office records, 1984-1988; RG0119 Series 19; 1.5 Linear feet (Box 1)
  This series includes Aladin pin, OCLC training manual, compact disc catalog, Gelman bookmarks, and renovation project information. They range in date from 1984-1988.
  Formerly ACC#455
- Building plans, 1966-1979; RG0119 Series 20; 1.5 Linear feet (Box 1)
  This series includes building plans and groundbreaking for new library, library regulations, floor plan transparencies, and photos (including groundbreaking). They range in date from 1966-1979.
  Formerly ACC#456
- Office records, 1977-1992; RG0119 Series 21; 4.5 Linear feet (Box 1, Box 2, Box 3)
  This series includes departmental files - cataloging, business office, building operations, media, reference, periodicals, circulation, committees, notis system, and personnel searches. They range in date from 1977-1992.
  Formerly ACC#461
  Scope and Contents
  Box 3: Electronic resources and reference; user ed planning; WRLC and consortium information; the publication "A private university with a public mandate" from 1987
- Photographs and negatives, 1979-1995; RG0119 Series 22; 1.5 Linear feet (Box 1)
  This series includes photos, negatives, slides of Gelman events, including Gelman 20th anniversary, Virginia campus, basketball exhibit, Crain medals donation, map exhibit, and Friends of the Libraries. They range in date from 1979-95.
  Formerly ACC#487
  - Office records, 1981-2000; RG0119 Series 49; 10.5 Linear feet
    This series includes chronological files, annual reports, SMG committee, administratives group meetings, PPG, briefing book for Trachtenberg, and oral history report. They range in date from 1981-2000.
    Formerly ACC#1006
    - Chronological files, 07/1991 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Chronological files, 01/1992-06/1992 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Chronological files, 01/1992-02/1992 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Chronological files, 03/1992-05/1992 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Chronological files, 05/1992 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Chronological files, 06/1992-07/1992 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Chronological files, 08/1992-09/1992 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Chronological files, 07/1992-01/1993 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Chronological files, 07/1993-09/1993 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Chronological files, 10/1993-11/1993 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Chronological files, 01/1994-06/13/1994 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Strategic Management and the United Way, undated (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Management Memos, undated (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Carlyle Systems, Inc: Tomus system, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 7)
      Three binders
    - Gelman Library annual report, 1993-1994 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Gelman Library annual report, 1994-1995 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Gelman Library annual report, 1995-1996 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Gelman Library annual report, 1996-1997 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Gelman Library annual report, 1997-1998 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Gelman Library annual report, 1998-1999 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - ARL Membership Submission, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - ARL Application, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - The ALA Yearbook, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Directory of Library Automation Software, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Building Operations, undated (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Photocopy machine proposals, undated (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - SMG, 1995-1996 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - SMG, 1997-1998 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - SMG, 1999-2000 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Benchmarking Workshop, 03/1999 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Administrative Group Meetings, 1991-1993 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Administrative Group Meetings, 1997-1998 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Administrative Group Meetings, 1998-1999 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Gelman Library Update, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - GW One-Card system, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Gelman Payroll development manual, 2000 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Equipment and Furniture, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Oral History Report, \1 ca.1985 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Collection Analysis project, 12/1981 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Proposal for CLSI automation of Gelman Library, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Information to Candidates for University Librarian, 08/1994 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - AUL for Collections Librarian search, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - UA GLIS Project Meeting, undated (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Enrollment Statistics, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Council of Librarians, 1988-1989 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Briefing Notebook for Stephan Joel Trachtenberg, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Departmental Statistics, 1994-1998 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - GWU Procurement and Procedures, 03/1990 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - GWorld Card, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Governor's Conference on Library and Information Services: Virginia, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - PPG, 01/1986-10/1987 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - PPG, 1992-1995 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - PPG, 1995-1996 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - March on Washington: Exhibit fund letters, 01/1999 (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Certificates, correspondence, 1939; RG0119 Series 23; .5 Linear feet (Flat box 1)
  This series includes certificates and correspondence with book - GW Medal in Tropical Medicine, 1939.
  Formerly ACC#504
- Publication layouts, 1980; RG0119 Series 24; 1.5 Linear Feet; 1.5 Linear feet
  This series includes two layouts for Gelman publications.
  Formerly ACC#510
  - Searching the CD catalog, 1980; RG00119 Series 24 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Guide to Gelman Library, 1980; RG0119 Series 24 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Office records, 1991-1993; RG0119 Series 25; 4.5 Linear feet (Box 3, Box 2, Box 1)
  This series includes files and correspondence from the University Librarian. They range in date from 1991-1993.
  Formerly ACC#518
- Photographs, negatives, 1979-1990; RG0119 Series 26; 1.5 Linear feet (Box 1)
  This series includes photos and negatives from Gelman events, Aladin system, Virginia campus, computers, Gelman exteriors, and work areas. They range in date from 1979-90.
  Formerly ACC#525
- Office records, 1985-1994; RG0119 Series 27; 4.5 Linear feet
  This series includes information on Operations Advisory Group (OAG), Policy and Planning Group (PPG) committee files, library update, and Friends of Library. They range in date from 1985-94.
  Formerly ACC#536
- Posters and postcards designed by Lance Hidy, circa 1995; RG0119 Series 28; .25 Linear feet (Map-folder 1)
  This series includes posters designed by Lance Hidy, including Gelman Library, vantage books - Ralph Waldo Emerson, Washington and Lee University, Boston public library, Corcoran Gallery exhibit, Lance Hidy electric art, and 7 postcard sized of other work. They are ca. 1995.
  Formerly ACC#543
- Photographs, 1995; RG0119 Series 29; 1.5 Linear feet (Box 1)
  This series includes photographs of staff association committee breakfast from Aug. 18, 1995.
  Formerly ACC#575
- Photographs, 1996; RG0119 Series 30; 0.25 Linear feet (Box 1)
  This series includes Gelman staff photographs from the summer of 1996.
  Formerly ACC#582
  - Photos of staff at Gelman Library, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Summer events
- Photographs, 1995; RG0119 Series 31; .25 Linear feet
  This series includes photographs of assistant university librarian Chris Filstrup at his farewell party from 1995.
  Formerly ACC#592. As of June 11, 2007, this series shares a box with RG0119/015 (formerly Acc436) and RG0119/030 (formerly Acc582)
- Blueprints, 1997; RG0119 Series 32; .25 Linear feet
  This series includes blueprints of Gelman Library technological upgrade project from July 1997 and 6th and 7th floor renovation from October 1997.
  Formerly ACC#715
  - Gelman Library technological upgrade project and 6th and 7th floor renovation, 07/1997-10/1997 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Upgrade project, July 1997; 6th and 7th floor renovation, October 1997.
- Photographs, undated; RG0119 Series 33; 1.5 Linear feet (Box 1)
  This series includes photographs of different events and staff, WWII exhibit, and others.
  Formerly ACC#722
  - Gelman Collection: Staff Photographs, 1993-1994 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Gelman Collection: Lost in the City (Colonnade Gallery), 01/27/1994-02/25/1994 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Gelman Collection: Lost in the City and African American Research Treasures, 02/05/1996-03/01/1996 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Gelman Collection: Gelman Library 20th Anniversary, 10/07/1993 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Gelman Collection: Cafe Gelman, undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Gelman Collection: Crain Collection: Political Memorabilia and American History, undated (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Gelman Collection: GW and WWII: A University and the War Effort, 05/11/1995-07/28/1995 (Box 1, Folder 7.1)
  - Gelman Collection: GW and WWII: A University and the War Effort, 05/11/1995-07/28/1995 (Box 1, Folder 7.2)
  - Gelman Collection: SPEC, various exhibits, functions, undated (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Gelman Collection: Staff, undated (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Office records, 1988-1997; RG0119 Series 34; 3 Linear feet (Box 2, Box 1)
  This series includes library updates, recruitment handbook, complaint/responses catalog binders, gift log binders, and professional travel. They range in date from 1988-97.
  Formerly ACC#726
- Office records, 1983-1995; RG0119 Series 35; 1.5 Linear feet (Box 1)
  This series includes information on University Librarian Sharon Rogers. The records include selected accomplishments from 1984-92, library annual reports, mission statement, strategic plans from 1983-1995.
  Formerly ACC#730
  - Drafts of "S.J. Rogers: Selected Accomplishments", 1984-1992 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Copies of Gelman Library Annual Report, 06/30/1990 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Statistical Summary for Fall, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - ACRL Statistics Questionnaire, 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Library Information Survey, Fall, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - ACRL Statistics Questionnaire, 1983-1984 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Library Information Survey, Fall, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Association of College and Research Libraries, Fall, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Strategic Plan, 1989-1992 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Strategic Plan, 1990-1993 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Strategic Plan, 1991-1994 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Melvin Gelman Library Mission Statement, undated (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Strategic Plan, 1992-1995 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Scholars' Express, undated (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Strategic Planning at Gelman Library, undated (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Gelman Library Strategic Plan, 1987-1990 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Office records, 1993-1997; RG0119 Series 36; 1.5 Linear feet (Box 1)
  This series includes information on Washington Research Library Consortium, strategic and business plans. They range in date from 1993-1997.
  Formerly ACC#731
  - Washington Reserach Library Consortium - Strategic and Business Plans, 1993-1997 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Office records, 1992; RG0119 Series 37; 1.5 Linear feet (Box 1)
  This series includes information on the Washington Research Library Consortium's background and chronology for building facility. These records are from 1992.
  Formerly ACC#735
- Videotape, RG0119 Series 38; .5 Linear feet (Box SHARED Box 20, Box 1)
  This series includes the videotape entitled "Changing Models of the American Family".
  Formerly ACC#754
- Newsletter, 1967-1975; RG0119 Series 39; 1.5 Linear feet (Box 1)
  This series includes a library newsletter from 1967-1975.
  Formerly ACC#800
  - Volume 1; No. 1 through 5, 09/1967-05/1968 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Volume 2; No. 1 through 5, 09/1968-05/1969 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Volume 3; No. 1 through 5, 09/1969-05/1970 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Volume 4; No. 1 through 5, 09/1970-05/1971 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Volume 5; No. 1 through 5, 09/1971-05/1972 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Volume 6; No. 1 through 4, 09/1972-06/1973 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Volume 7; No. 1 through 4, 10/1973-04/1974 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Volume 8; No. 1 through 5, 09/1974-06/1975 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Volume 9; No. 1 through 2, 09/1975-11/1975 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Contact prints, 1998; RG0119 Series 40; 1.5 Linear feet (Box 1)
  This series includes contact prints from Gelman Library's 25th anniversary celebration in April 1998.
  Formerly ACC#807
- Office records, 1992-1998; RG0119 Series 41; 6 Linear feet
  This series includes files, correspondence, from the University Librarian. They range in date from 1992-98.
  Formerly ACC#818
- Photographs, 2000; RG0119 Series 42; 1.5 Linear feet (Box 1)
  This series includes photos of the Gelman Library staff (some are labeled). These photos were taken in Spring 2000.
  Formerly ACC#830
- Photographs and negatives, 1999-2000; RG0119 Series 43; .25 Linear feet (Box 1)
  This series includes negatives and photos from the Gelman staff picnic at Mt. Vernon campus in August 1999; staff appreciation awards; Assistant University Librarian David Nutty's farewell (feb. 2000); Scott Stebleman's farewell, 2000.
  Formerly ACC#834
- Office records, 1983-1994; RG0119 Series 44; 55.5 Linear feet
  This series includes surveys, budget information, job applicants, personnel, subject specialists, and strategic plan. They range in date from 1983-94.
  Formerly ACC#840
- Photographs, 1980-1989; RG0119 Series 45; 6 Linear feet (Box 1, Box 2, Box 3, Box 4)
  This series includes photographs of Gelman Library - individuals, staff, events, and buildings- taken by Jonathan Melegrito (former head of circulation department). They are ca 1980's.
  Formerly ACC#842
- Accession logs, 1877-1969; RG0119 Series 46; 25.5 Linear feet
  This series includes library accession logs from 1877 and 1900s-1960s.
  Formerly ACC#942
  - Accession Log Vol. O-1 (105,001 - 110,000), August, 1947 - August, 1948; This accession log records book accessions made by The George Washington University library between August 1, 1947 - August 17, 1948. Different than the older Dewey Accession Logs, this log is typewritten and includes details on 18,800 items acquired during that time. Details noted include the accessions' title, author, date acquired, volume number, cost, publication year, and source including various donors. Handwritten notations of withdrawal or discarding included on some items in the margins. Folder 1/4 of Volume O, rehoused from original binder into folders. (Box 6, Folder 1)
    Melvin Gelman Library; Gelman Library; Lisner Library; Library Administration
  - Donations to the Library of Columbian University, 1877-1891 (Box 7)
    General
    The book only has about the first 70 pages filled out.
- Reports and memos, RG0119 Series 47; 58.5 Linear feet (Box 1, Box 2, Box 3, Box 4, Box 5, Box 6, Box 7, Box 8, Box 9, Box 10, Box 11, Box 12, Box 13, Box 14, Box 15, Box 16, Box 17, Box 18, Box 19, Box 20, Box 21, Box 22, Box 23, Box 24, Box 25, Box 26, Box 27, Box 28, Box 29, Box 30, Box 31, Box 32, Box 33, Box 34, Box 35, Box 36, Box 37, Box 38, Box 39)
  This series includes memos and reports of the library and Special Collections department.
  Formerly ACC#944; MANY OF THE MATERIALS IN THIS COLLECTION ARE DUPLICATED ELSEWHERE AND ARE NON-RECORD MATERIALS TO BE CULLED AND DISPOSED OF
- T-shirts, 1993-1998; RG0119 Series 48; 1.5 Linear feet (Box 1)
  This series includes six t-shirts from Caf Gelman and other events ranging from 1993-1998.
  Formerly ACC#978
  - Cafe Gelman, Banned Books Week, undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Opening Convocation, 09/01/1998 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Cafe Gelman "Savor the Flavor", 04/14/1994 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Cafe Gelman, Banned Books Week, 09/29/1994 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Gelman Library 20th Anniversary, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Gelman Library - "Aladin's New Voyage" (new catalog system), 1997 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Office records, 1994-1997; RG0119 Series 50; 7.5 Linear feet
  This series includes records concerning ARL membership, friends of the libraries, special collections exhibits and events, SMG meetings, and strategic planning. They range in date from 1994-97.
  Formerly ACC#1012
  - Working File: Association of Research Libraries, undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Association of Research Libraries File, undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Association of Research Libraries Material, undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Association of Research Libraries Membership Applications, undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Working File: Associate University Librarian Info Services, undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Working File: Associate University Librarian Info Tech, undated (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Budget, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Budget, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Cafe Gelman - Fall, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Working File: CANU, undated (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Working File: Classification Study, undated (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Working File: Community Service Volunteers, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Columbian College of Arts and Sciences - 001-32-Fall, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Working File: CSU, undated (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Working File: Danish Exhibit, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Working File: Bob Traux: My Life ..., undated (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Working File: Columbian College of Arts and Sciences 001, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Working File: Columbian School of Arts and Sciences, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Events: American Women Composers Concert, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Faculty Workshop - Spring, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Working File: Friends Board, 1996-1997 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Working File: Friends Dinner, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Working File: GLIS Open House - Fall, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Working File: Gifts Workshop, undated (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Working File: Grad Student Fair, undated (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Working File: Hatchet Editors Lunch, 09/19/1997 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Working File: Hidy Promo, 1996-1997 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Working File: JSTOR Demo - Fall, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Working File: KSA Fundraising Event, 04/1997 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Working File: Library Review, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Working File: Library Update, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Working File: Library Update, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Working File: New Faculty Orientation, 09/22/1996 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Working File: Presidential Inauguration, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Working File: SMGSC, 1996-1997 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Working File: Special Collections Exhibit, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Working File: SPEC Exhibits, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Working File: Staff Recognition Awards, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Working File: Strategic Planning Retreat, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Working File: Strategic Planning Retreat, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Working File: Strategic Planning Presentation, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Working File: Student Association Luncheon, 09/12/1997 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Working File: Carrie Potter - SA President, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Working File: Symposium, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Working File: Student Orientation Committee, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Working File: SYSLAN, 1996-1997 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Working File: 5-Year Plan, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Working File: Video Free Earth Donor Recognition, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Working File: Welcome Week, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Working File: WRLC Library Survey, 1996-1997 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Working File: WRLC Resource Sharing Statistics, undated (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Working File: Quarterly Open Forums, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Working File: Public Relations Literature, undated (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Reference Librarian/Social Sciences Subject Specialist, undated (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Quarterly Open Furm, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - SAC/Staff Appreciation Breakfast, undated (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Working File: Sample Description - Associate/Assistant, undated (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Search: Catologer/Subject Specific for Slavic Language and Literature, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - SMGSC, 1995-1996 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Senior Class Gifts, undated (Box 3, Folder 9)